cornerstoneconfessions.com 2019-03-04

# Cornerstone Confessions Privacy Policy

##### **Here at Cornerstone Confessions, your privacy  is valued!  The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you what personally identifiable information Cornerstone Confessions may collect and how it may be used.**

**Information You Voluntarily Submit to the website**

Cornerstone Confessions may collect personal information from you such as your name or email address. For example, you may voluntarily submit information to the website by leaving a comment, subscribing to a newsletter, making a purchase, or submitting a contact form. If as a user or customer you create a user profile, which allows you to create a username and password, Cornerstone Confessions will store the username, but your password will not be visible in our records.

**Automatically-Collected Information** : Cornerstone Confessions automatically collects certain information about you and the device with which you access the website. For example, when you use the website, Cornerstone Confessions will log your IP address, operating system type, browser type, referring website, pages you viewed, and the dates/times when you accessed the website. Cornerstone Confessions may also collect information about actions you take when using the website, such as links clicked.

**Cookies** : Cornerstone Confessions may log information using cookies, which are small data files stored on your browser by the Cornerstone Confessionsbsite. Cornerstone Confessions may use both session cookies, which expire when you close your browser, and persistent cookies, which stay on your browser until deleted, to provide you with a more personalized experience on the website.

Cornerstone Confessions may use the information collected in the following ways:

  * To operate and maintain the website;
  * To create your account, identify you as a user of the website, and customize the website for your account;
  * To send you promotional information, such as newsletters. Each email promotion will provide information on how to opt-out of future mailings;
  * To send you administrative communications, such as administrative emails, confirmation emails, technical notices, updates on policies, or security alerts;
  * To respond to your comments or inquiries;
  * To provide you with user support;
  * To track and measure advertising on the website;
  * To protect, investigate, and deter against unauthorized or illegal activity.

Cornerstone Confessions may share your information with third parties for marketing and analysis purposes. Each third-party service provider’s use of your personal information is dictated by their respective privacy policies.The Cornerstone Confessions website currently uses the following third-party service providers:

**Google Analytics**  – This service tracks website usage and provides information such as referring websites and user actions on the website. Google Analytics may capture your IP address, but no other personal information is captured by Google Analytics.

**MadMimi**  – This service is used for delivery of email updates and newsletters. Cornerstone Confessions store your name and email address for purposes of delivering such communications.  Please refer to [MadMimi’s privacy policy](https://madmimi.com/legal/terms) for further information.

**Feed.press** – This service is used to send you push notifications through your web browser, should you choose.  Please refer to [Feed.press’s privacy policy](https://onesignal.com/privacy_policy) for further information.

**Facebook**  – Your email address and name may be used to create custom audiences on Facebook.That data is hashed, anonymous, and used only according to Facebook’s terms here <https://www.facebook.com/legal/terms/customaudience>

**Monumetrics  – **This service tracks website usage and user actions in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest.  No other personal information is captured.  Please refer to [Monumetrics’ privacy policy](https://www.monumetric.com/privacy-policy/) for further information.

At this time, your personal information is not shared with any other third-party applications. This list may be amended from time to time at Cornerstone Confessions’s sole discretion.

Except when required by law, Cornerstone Confessions will not sell, distribute, or reveal your email addresses or other personal information without your consent; however Cornerstone Confessions may disclose or transfer personal information collected through the website to third parties who acquire all or a portion of our business, which may be the result of a merger, consolidation, or purchase of all or a portion of our assets, or in connection with any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding brought by or against us.

From time to time, Cornerstone Confessions may use anonymous data, which does not identify you alone, or when combined with data from other parties. This type of anonymous data may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Examples of this anonymous data may include analytics or information collected from cookies.

If you create a user profile on the Cornerstone Confessions website or leave a comment, certain information may be publicly visible.  To create a user profile, you must choose a username and password and input your email address for profile confirmation.  Your email address will never be available publicly.  At your option, you may also add an avatar, a profile description, and a link to your website. Users may see your username, avatar, profile description and website information.

The website uses cookies to store visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, customize website content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends. Cookies may also be used by third-party services, such as Google Analytics, as described herein.

Users may, at any time, prevent the setting of cookies, by the website, by using a corresponding setting of your internet browser and may thus permanently deny the setting of cookies. Furthermore, already set cookies may be deleted at any time via an Internet browser or other software programs. This is possible in all popular Internet browsers. However, if users deactivate the setting of cookies in your Internet browser, not all functions of our website may be entirely usable.

## **Display Ads**

Cornerstone Confessions uses third-party advertising companies to serve content and advertisements when you visit the website. These ads may rely on the use of cookies, as noted above.

## **Retargeting  Ads**

From time to time, the website may engage in remarketing efforts with third-party companies, such as Google, Facebook, or Instagram, in order to market. These companies use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the website.

Third parties, including Facebook, may use cookies, web beacons, and other storage technologies to collect or receive specific types of information and use that information  
to provide targeted ads to you on other platforms. Cornerstone Confessions uses the Conversion Tracking Pixel service of Facebook, Inc. for marketing and advertising purposes. This tool allows us to follow the actions of users on our site in order to create Facebook ads, target ads to potentially interested audiences, and analyze the efficacy of Facebook ads. The data collected via the pixel is anonymous. This means that Cornerstone Confessions cannot see the personal data of any individual user collected by the pixel; however, the collected data are saved and processed by Facebook.

Facebook is able to connect the data with your Facebook account and use the data for their own advertising purposes, in accordance with Facebook’s Data Use Policy found  
at https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/. Facebook Conversion Tracking also allows Facebook and its partners to show you advertisements on and outside Facebook.

You may opt-out of this data collection and the use of your information for ad targeting by adjusting your Facebook ad preferences, using one of these two links (depending on  
which device you are using at the moment):

  * MOBILE ​​<https://m.facebook.com/ads/preferences/settings/>​
  * DESKTOP <https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads>

To learn more about what information ad networks collect about you, and to opt out, see this tool http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2#!/

## **Affiliate Program Participation**

The website may engage in affiliate marketing, which is done by embedding tracking links into the website. If you click on a link for an affiliate partnership, a cookie will be placed on your browser to track any sales for purposes of commissions.

Cornerstone Confessions is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and links to Amazon.com.  As part of this Amazon Associates program, the website will post customized links, provided by Amazon, to track the referrals to their website. This program utilizes cookies to track visits for the purposes of assigning commission on these sales.

## **Newsletters**

On the Cornerstone Confessionsbsite, you may subscribe to our newsletter, which may be used for advertising purposes. All newsletters sent may contain tracking pixels. The pixel is embedded in emails and allows an analysis of the success of online marketing campaigns. Because of these tracking pixels, Cornerstone Confessions may see if and when you open an email and which links within the email you click. Also, this allows the website to adapt the content of future newsletters to the interests of the user. This behavior will not be passed on to third parties.

  * Opt-out – You may opt-out of future email communications by following the unsubscribe links in our emails. You may also notify us at kathy@cornerstoneconfessions.com to be removed from our mailing list.
  * Access – You may access the personal information Cornerstone Confessions have about you by submitting a request to kathy@cornerstoneconfessions.com.
  * Amend – You may contact us at kathy@cornerstoneconfessions.com to amend or update your personal information.
  * Forget – In certain situations, you may request that Cornerstone Confessions erase or forget your personal data. To do so, please submit a request to kathy@cornerstoneconfessions.com.

Please note that Cornerstone Confessions may need to retain certain information for record keeping purposes or to complete transactions, or when required by law.

At no time should you submit sensitive personal information to the Cornerstone Confessions’ website. This includes your social security number, information regarding race or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious beliefs, health information, criminal background, or trade union memberships. If you elect to submit such information to us, it will be subject to this Privacy Policy.

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from anyone under 16 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 16 years old or older.  If a parent or guardian believes that the website has personally identifiable information of a child under the age of 16 in its database, please contact us immediately at kathy@cornerstoneconfessions.com so we can remove such information from our records.

At any time, please contact us at kathy@cornerstoneconfessions.com for questions related to this Privacy Policy.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

_Last updated: May 22, 2018._
